barrystickets.com 2012-12-29

# Barrys Tickets - Privacy Policy

| 

## Barry's Tickets - Privacy Policy

**Barrystickets.com Privacy Policy**

Member Information and Registration To use Barrystickets.com basic features you do not have to divulge any personal information. Some forms will contain optional questions, which help us improve the usefulness of this site. Required fields will always be clearly marked to distinguish them from optional fields.

No individual personal information about you will be shared with anybody, without your permission, and will only be used by Barrystickets.com and its licensed partners. Some demographic information may be shared in aggregate form with reputable third parties for advertising purposes (i.e. delivering online ads or taking you to Web sites that best match your interests). Examples of giving permission are selecting the opt-in option on a registration form or taking part in a contest sponsored by a third party. 

In the event that Barrystickets.com is acquired by or merged with a third party, individual personal information may be transferred to the third party pursuant to such acquisition or merger. If an aquisition or merger does occur you will be notified via email and instructions for removing your registration information will be included in that email. 

WE DO NOT SELL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OR EMAIL ADDRESS TO "LIST BROKERS" OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTY.

  * **How the Information is Used**

>   
>  The special features on our site require the majority of the information we request in order to function properly. The other information and optional questions give us additional information about our user base that helps us improve the site. 

  * **Who Collects the Information**

>   
>  Any information you submit while registering for Barrystickets.com features or promotions is collected solely by Barry's Ticket Service Inc.
> 
> When registering for a co-branded feature or promotion, your information may be collected by both Barrystickets.com and the sponsor, or collected by one then shared with the other. 

  * **Information Distribution**

>   
>  Your personal information will not be shared with anyone unless you grant Barrystickets.com permission to do so. Barrystickets.com will often host a contest with a third-party sponsor. By entering these contests you give permission to exchange some or all of your personal information. 

  * **Afffiliate Program**

>   
>  When you sign up to our affiliate program, we collect the necessary information to be able to pay you if you generate any sale. We need your full name, your current address, your email, and your website. Checks are sent on the 25th of each month. 

  * **Opt Out From PII**

>   
>  We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or by emailing us at info@Barrystickets.com or you may contact us at 800-801-8425 to opt-out. 

  * **Update your personal information**

>   
>  If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by contacting us by telephone at 800-801-8425. 

  * **Member Contact**

>   
>  By signing up for Barrystickets.com email you give Barrystickets.com permission, that from time to time Barrystickets.com may contact you by electronic or postal mail so that you can receive information, savings or special offers that relate directly to the information you have provided.

  * **Control**

>   
>  If you have provided information and wish in the future that we stop using this information or stop sharing it with third parties, or if you wish to update or change your information, you can send us your request at [info@barrystickets.com](mailto:info@Barrystickets.com). Barrystickets.com encourages you to keep your profile updated, including both the personal information you submit and your preferences for features and services. You can request changes by sending us email at[ info@barrystickets.com](mailto:info@barrystickets.com) . 

  * **Procedures Used to Protect Data**

>   
>  Barrystickets.com uses password protection and firewalls that meet industry standards to protect all data. Access to user data is restricted to authorized personnel. Barrystickets.com will regularly evaluate its security solutions and take any steps necessary to keep the site and the data secure.

  * **Registration**

>   
>  Barrys Tickets is the sole owner of the information collected on www.barrystickets.com. Barry's Tickets collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site (name, email address and your interest to receive newsletters, and personal identifications such as credit cards when you buy from us). Our web hosting partner is "[Simplicity Hosting](http://www.simplicityhosting.com/)." 

  * **Credit Card Security**

>   
>  The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at[ info@Barrystickets.com](mailto:%20info@barrystickets.com). We use other third parties to protect credit card transactions on our site. When you buy with us, we share your name, address and credit card information for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. VeriSign is our credit card partner; you can review their privacy statement by [Clicking Here](http://www.verisign.com/Privacy/index.html). 

  * **Orders**

>   
>  If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. If would like to receive discounts and special events, just check the box when you purchase an order. 

  * **Links from the Site**

>   
>  Users should be aware that Barrystickets.com does not endorse or guarantee the accuracy, integrity, validity or quality of the contests and promotions listed within this directory except for those that are directly administered by Barrystickets.com. Before entering any contest, it is recommended that you read and understand the hosts' privacy policy and the rules and restrictions pertaining to that contest. 

  * **Cookies**

>   
>  A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Our Web site also uses "cookie" technology to make your visits more convenient. You are free to reject or "not accept" all Barrystickets.com cookies. If you reject the cookies you will still be able to use all of Barrystickets.com features, but we will not be able to customize your future visits. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners (Yahoo Search Marketing) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

  * **Contacting Barrystickets.com**

>   
>  When a user contacts Barrystickets.com for customer support, Barrystickets.com does not retain any personal information from that correspondence. We may store the messages to track different site issues, but we will never add those users to our mailing list. Barrystickets.com will only respond to those messages that require a response. 

  * **Shipping**

>   
>  We use other third parties to provide shipping on our site. When you sign up for shipping, we will share your name and address for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. You can review FedEx privacy statement by [Clicking Here](http://www.fedex.com/us/privacypolicy.html). 

  * **Sales**

>   
>  If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

  * **Legal Statement**

>   
>  We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

  * **Notification of changes**

>   
>  If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

  * **TRUSTe**

>   
>  Barry's Ticket Services Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the[ site](http://www.barrystickets.com/privacy.php). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact info at [info@barrystickets.com](mailto:info@barrystickets.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. Effective date: April 18, 2006 

  * **Location & Phone number**

>   
>  Our main office is located   
>  23622 Calabasas Road, Suite 123   
>  Calabasas CA 91302  
>  (818) 990-8499 

  * **Questions?**

>   
>  Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Barrystickets.com's site coordinator at [info@barrystickets.com](mailto:info@barrystickets.com)
